We're ready now to talk about how this hem is going to look when we're, when we're finished.
We need to turn it under and pin it, but let me show you why we are going to pin it the way we do.
So, like we said, this first mark is our new hem length. This mark is going to be the top of the cuff.
This mark is the bottom of the cuff.
And this mark is what's turned underneath.
This this hem is what's turned underneath and hidden away on the inside of the pants.
So, when we do this cuff, what we want to do is, make sure this is on top, this is going to be right at the top.
And it's going to be up here.
And this mark and this mark are both one and and one-fourth inch away from the top of the cuff.
So, what we want to do is make this mark and this mark meet.
And so we just want to grab this mark, and just pinch it, just like this so it is there on top.
And just bring it over.
Your going to hold it.
And you can see.
There's a mark here and a mark here.
I'll have to put my thumb there.
My fingernail.
Feel it.
I can tell that it is right there on top.
But if you're not quite for sure, just grab a pin, and just stick it in, right where that one mark is and bring it out and look it goes right through to the other mark.
So, I know that's perfectly where I need it.
And, so since we know that.
This is what the hem is going to look like.
We're just going to fold it up again so you can see how well that's going to look.
So, like I said, this is the top of the cuff and the bottom of the cuff.
And the final hem.
So, in the next clip.
I'll show you how to pin it all the way around and then we'll close it up in a few steps later.
So, let's get started pinning this down.